A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, General Files (Room 5600), 2001-2006, RG 55 FA1254
Rockefeller Archive Center
Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, General Files (Room 5600), 2001-2006, RG 55
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman (1910-2004)
FA1254
27.64 Cubic Feet 71 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box, 1 half-letter document box
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted in accordance with the terms of donation from the Laurance S. Rockefeller estate (January 2009). Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Original order. Alphabetical, in series, primarily by subject/topic.
Scope and Contents
The 2001-2006 general files chronicle continued management of the philanthropic affairs of Laurance S. Rockefeller.
Over the years the Rockefeller family has been involved in virtually all aspects of modern philanthropy at the local, national and international levels through their foundation activities as well as their individual personal giving. Major interests include: physical and mental health, conservation, education, economics, international relations, medicine and science, politics, population, religion, social welfare, the visual and performing arts, cultural exchange programs, and economic and social development of underdeveloped areas. While Laurance S. Rockefeller naturally began to reduce his public schedule and activities in the later years of his life and career, the vast scope and breadth of his philanthropic interests continued in much of the same subject matter.
The general files primarily consist of correspondence, reports, pamphlets, memoranda, charters and certificates of incorporation, minutes and meeting records as well as documentation of contributions, finance and investment materials, real estate and properties, newspaper clippings, diaries, notebooks, calendars, and printed material.
- Audiovisual Material, A
  Moving Images
  - Conservation - Murie Center - Arti Dance - The Mardy Murie Story (Box T1)
    Scope and Contents
    Narrated by Harrison Ford.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copy currently unavailable. Contact a RAC archivist for further assistance.
  - Education - Radio and TV - KCTS, The Public Radio Network - Red, White and Buddha Sample Tape, VHS, 9 minutes. (Box T1)
    Access copy currently unavailabe. Please contact a RAC archivist for further assistance.
    Producer - Lisa Hardmeyer.
- A-E, 2001-2006; 1
  - Agriculture - A-Z (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Includes: Glynwood Center; Stone Barns Center for Agriculture.
  - Agriculture - American Farmland Trust, 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Appeals - Domestic - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 3-10, Box 2, Folder 1-3)
    Includes: American Fund for Charities; American Hiking Society; Americas Wildlife; Ancient Order of Hibernians in America; Anderson, Eleanor W.; Anderson, Mr. and Mrs. Keith; Auspex Entertainment; Avner Leviev Torah Center; Bennett, John G., Jr.; Berry Ray; Bertoncelj, Juanita, PhD; Bluebird Recovery Program Inc.; BodhGara; Bruenn, Peter L.; Burberick, Stanford V.; Cangemi, Phyllis; Carolina Health Careers Inc.; Davis, Mr. and Mrs. Robert Olen; Dolphin Project; Donahoe, Allyson; Elliott, Mike; Environmental Defense; Fein, Jonathan; Friends of the Jackson Laboratory; Garcia, Juanita; Genefit Nutrition, LLC; Gordon, Nick; Hamilton, Keith; Holzer, Hans; Iguana Fundraising Solutions; International Dendrological Research Institute; Johnson, Linda R.; Johnston, Jill; Kozlovich, Eli; Lahi, Iana; Le Bonheur Club Inc.; Lewis, Zania; Linville Central Rescue Squad; Luce, Henry, III; Mason, Sarah L.; Monastery of St. Gertrude; Mt. Crotchet Firefighters Association; Natural Light Studios; New Tang Dynasty Television; Newhall, Ashton; Nitsch, Susanne; Noorzai, Mariam; Northwest Trek Wildlife Park; One Cosmos; Oubre, Alondra, PhD; Pastell, Margaret; Pattison, Alice Chen; PONYCAB; Praderio, Marco; Puketapu, Kara; R.A.R.E.; Riveriew Foundation; Rozga, Eliane; Schwerin, Noel; Seaman, Judy; Senior Gleaners Inc.; Stevenson, Scotty; Taft Group; Tai Hsuan Foundation; Talen, Bill; Territory; Thaheld, Fred H.; Thurlow, Lord; Transparent Commerce.Org; Warren Seabury Management of Public Relations; Woolschlager, Erin.
  - Appeals - Domestic - Infinity Group Productions, 2001-2006 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Appeals - Domestic - Bob Thurman Proposals, 2001-2006 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Appeals - Foreign - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Includes: Agnes, Namta; Cartier, J.S.; East Africa - Wabulya, Elizabeth; Ellis, John S. (Removed by Liz Haviland, Family Office, October 2006); Erin House; Liddle, Dr. P.H.; Oppermann, Fabien; Reyes, Robert, Jr.; Vance, Peter; West Africa - Farowen.
  - Architecture - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Includes: American Institute of Architects.
  - Aviation - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Includes Air Group Inc.; Flight Safety Foundation; Piasecki Aircraft Corporation; Smith, Lawrence B.
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - A-Z (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Includes: Colonial Williamsburg Presidential Discretionary Endowment Fund.
  - Defense - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Includes: Institute for Defense Analyses.
  - Economics - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Includes: American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research.
- Arts, 2001-2006; 2
  - Arts - A-D, 2001-2006 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Includes: American Associates of the Royal Academy Trust; American Federation of the Arts; Arts International; Art-Talk; Big Apple Circus; Center for the Arts; Creative Time; Drawing Center.
  - Arts - E-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
    Includes: EcoArts; Empire State Plaza Art Collection and Plaza Memorials; Falcon Heart Studios; Hispanic Society of America; John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts; Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts Inc.; Municipal Art Society; National Book Festival Gala; New York Foundation for the Arts; Pentangle Council on the Arts; Duncan Phillips Awards; Phillips de Pury and Luxembourg; Princess Grace Foundation - USA; Roger Keverne (removed by Liz Haviland, Family Office, October 2006); Rolex Mentor and Protege Arts Initiative (not in file, SVP [Family Office], November 29, 2007; Christine Roussel Studios; Storm King Art Center; Studio in a School; Town Hall; Westchester Arts Council; World Monuments Fund.
  - Americans for the Arts, 2001-2006 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Art Production Fund (Yvonne Force, Inc.), 2001-2006 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bethesda Academy of Performing Arts, 2001-2006 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Community Center for the Arts, 2001-2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Vermont Folklife Studio, 2001-2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Vermont Studio Center, 2001-2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Appraisals - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Includes: Christie's - Japanese and Korean Art; Sotheby's - Sale Statement.
  - Books - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Includes: Christmas Book Project.
  - Dance - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Includes: American Contemporary Ballet; Dance Theatre of Harlem; New York City Ballet.
  - Films - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
    Includes: Berga: Soldiers of Another War; Contrasting Perspectives Inc.; Crown Sephira Productions; Davis, Devra Lee, PhD, MPH (Film Proposal); Dirty Cricket Films Inc. (removed by Liz Haviland, Family Office, October 2006); Film Odyssey (not in file, SVP [Family Office], November 29, 2007); "Finding Father"; Guggenheim Productions Inc.; Hudson River Special; Maidstone Studios; Manchester Film Festival; Media Works International; New Story Productions; Persistent Productions; Sacred Land Film Project; Wild Oak Pictures.
  - Films - Lemle Pictures Inc. (New York Open Center), 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Films - Tatge - Lasseur Productions, 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Galleries - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Includes: Berry-Hill Galleries Inc.; Falcon Heart Studios; JG Contemporary; Marlborough Gallery Inc.; Mitchell-Innes and Nash Gallery; Mt. San Antonio College Art Gallery; Gerald Peters Gallery; Royal-Athena Galleries; Joan Whalen Fine Art.
  - Journalism - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Includes Livingston Awards for Young Journalists.
  - Libraries - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Includes: American Merchant Marine Library Association; Elmer Holmes Bobst Library; Chilmark Public Library; Leetonia Community Public Library; New York Public Library; Richard Nixon Library and Birthplace; Princeton Public Library; Smithsonian Institute - Archives Photography Exhibition.
  - Libraries - Library of Congress, 2001-2006 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
    Includes: James Madison Council and John W. Kluge Center.
  - Libraries - Redwood Library and Athenaeum, 2001-2006 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Libraries - Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt Institute, 2001-2006 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Libraries - Norman Williams Public Library, 2001-2006 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Museums - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 6, Folder 1-6)
    Includes: Adirondack Museum; American Friends of the Shanghai Museum; American Museum of Natural History; Asian Art Museum; Autry National Center; Bristol-Myers Squibb Company; Brooklyn Museum of Art; Colter Bay Museum; Cranbrook Art Museum; Frazier Historical Arms Museum; Frick Collection; Hudson River Maritime Museum; Reginald F. Lewis Museum of Maryland African American History and Culture; McLean County Historical and Genealogical Museum; Museum for African Art; Museum of the City of New York; Museum of Comparative Zoology; Museum Exchange Program; Museum of Man in the Sea; Natural History Museum of the Adirondacks; Naval Aviation Museum Foundation; Queens Museum of Art; Norman Rockwell Museum; P.S. 1 Contemporary Art Center; San Antonio Museum of Art; Shelburne Museum; Smithsonian Institution - A-Z; Smithsonian Institution - Archives of American Art; Smithsonian Institution - National Gallery of Art; Smithsonian Institution - National Museum of African Art; Weaver Castle Museum; Whitney Museum of American Art.
  - Museums - Admiral Nimitz Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Museums - Buffalo Bill Historical Center, 2001-2006 (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
  - Museums - Wendell Gilley Museum, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Museums - Historic New Amsterdam, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Museums - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Museums - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Museums - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Museums - Mystic Seaport Museum, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Museums - National Museum of Wildlife Art, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Museums - South Street Seaport Museum, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Museums - Western Heritage Center, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Music - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Includes: American Friends of the AIx-en-Provence Music Festival; American Friends of the Israel Philharmonic Orchestra; Gloriae Dei Artes; Gloriae Dei Cantores; Healing the Divide; New Orleans Opera Association; Orchestra of St. Luke's; Society of Singers.
  - Music - American Composers Orchestra, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Music - Carnegie Hall, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Music - Grand Teton Music Festival, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Music - Metropolitan Opera Association, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Music - Opera Colorado, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Paintings - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Includes: Coral Bay Community Council.
  - Poetry - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Academy of American Poets. Tucson Poetry Festival.
  - Publications - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 8-9)
    Includes: Emerald Partners (Bessie Dashiell Book); Forbes Magazine; Free Press; New York, New Yorker II (New York Magazine); New York Observer; New York Times - Rockefeller's Legacy of Roads; New York Times (LSR letters and responses; June 19, 2002); Robb Report Worth (2 copies); Town and Country; Vermont Standard; Washington Post; Worth (The Good We Do, February 2004).
  - Publication - Hudson Valley Writer's Center, 2001-2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Publications - Island Press, 2001-2006 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Restorations - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Includes: Friends of the Zorach Fountain; Landmarks Conservancy; Olana Partnership (formerly Friends of Olana); Preservation League of New York State.
  - Restorations - New York Landmarks Conservancy, 2001-2006 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Restorations - Versailles Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
  - Theatre - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Includes: Helen Hayes Awards.
  - Theatre - Apollo Theater Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Civic, 2001-2006; 3
  - Civic - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
    Includes: Citizens for Global Solutions; Community Coalition; Community Funds Inc.; Indian Harbor Volunteer Fire Department; Military Tribute to Bob Hope; National Association of State Public Interest Groups; National Smoke, Fire, and Burn Institute; New York Public Interest Research Group Fund; Teago Volunteer Fire Department; Village of Sleepy Hollow.
  - Battery Conservancy (Conservancy for Historic Battery Park), 2001-2006 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Common Good, 2001-2006 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
  - Common Sense Institute Inc., 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Landmark Volunteers, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Mount Pleasant Police Benevolent Association, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - People for the American Way, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - New York City - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
  - New York City - Citizens Committee for New York City, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - New York City - Correctional Association of New York, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - New York City - New 42nd Street, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Clubs, 2001-2006; 4
  - Clubs - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Includes: Cosmopolitan Club; Cosmos Club; Knickerbocker Club; Lakota Club; Lotos Club; Round Table; Thursday Club (Breuer [House?] Tour); University Club; Wings Club; Woodstock Country Club.
  - Ivy Club, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Princeton University
  - Sleepy Hollow Country Club, 2001-2006 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    WGA Caddie Scholarship Fund
- Conservation, 2001-2006; 5
  - Conservation - A-B, 2001-2006 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    Includes: Acoustic Ecology Institute; Alaska Conservation Foundation; Amazon Conservation Team; American Bird Conservancy; American Corn Growers Foundation; American Forests; American P.I.E. (American Public Information on the Environment); Anacostia Watershed Society; Appalachian Trail Conservancy; Archaeological Conservancy; Audubon Connecticut; Bear Trust International; Blake Hill Property; Blue Goose Alliance; W. Haywood Burns Environmental Education Center Inc.; Butterfly Discovery Park (Coevolution Institute).
  - Conservation - C-E, 2001-2006 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Includes: Calstart; Caretta Research Project (removed by Liz Haviland, Family Office, October 2006); Center for Environmental Research and Conservation; Children's Health Environmental Coalition; City Parks Alliance; Connecticut Chapter of the Nature Conservancy; Conservation Trust of Puerto Rico; Council on Environmental Quality; Dominicans of St. Catharine; Earth Charter; Earth Day 2002; Earth Pledge Foundation; Eastern National; Elm Research Institute; Eloika Lake Association; Empire State Task Force for Land and Water Conservation Funding; Environmental Alliance for Senior Involvement; EnviroMentors.
  - Conservation - F-L, 2001-2006 (Box 13, Folder 1-4)
    Includes: Foundation for Wildlife Conservation Inc.; Friends of Haleakala National Park; Friends of the Rockefeller State Park Preserve (Mice Project); Friends of Van Cortlandt Park; Green Guide Institute; Green River Valley Land Trust; Greenbelt Conservancy Inc.; Hastings Center; High Ridge Farms; Holland Island Preservation Foundation: Hudson River Environmental Society; Hudson River Sloop, Clearwater, Inc.; Hudson River Valley National Heritage Area; Hyde Hall; INFORM Inc.; International Society for Ecology and Culture; Interstate Commission on the Potomac River Basin; Jackson Hole Conservation Alliance; Lyndon B. Johnson National Historical Park; Journal of the American Shore and Beach Preservation Association; Kentucky Natural Lands Trust; Land Trust Alliance; Land Trust International; Land Use and Society (Rutherford H. Platt) (not in file, SVP, Family Office, December 4, 2007); Leadership Committee for Parks 2001; Live and Let Live Farm Inc.; Loon Preservation Committee. Materials concerning Florestra and Frommer's National Parks removed by Liz Haviland, Family Office, October 2006.
  - Conservation - M-P, 2001-2006 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Includes: MAGIC (Maryland Alliance for Greenway Improvement and Conservation); Maine Coast Heritage Trust; Maine Lakes Conservancy Institute; Minneapolis Parks Legacy Society (not in file, SVP, Family Office, December 4, 2007); Samuel Morse Historic Site; Mothers and Others for a Livable Planet; National Aquarium in Baltimore; National Center for the American Revolution; National Environmental Trust; Nature and Culture International; New England Conservatory; New England Forestry Foundation; North Dakota Natural Resources Trust; Oregon Trout; Parks 2001; Partnership for the Delaware Estuary Inc.; Peace Parks Foundation (removed by Liz Haviland, Family Office, October 2006); Prairie Biotic Research Inc.; PRBO Conservation Science.
  - Conservation - Q-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
    Includes: Rails-to-Trails; Residents' Committee to Protect the Adirondacks; Santa Fe Conservation Trust; Save Our Undeveloped Land; Smokey House Center; Sonoran Institute; South Florida Resource Conservation and Development Council Inc.; Sprawl Watch Clearinghouse; Trust for Public Land; Trustees of Reservations; United Mountain Defense; Watts Branch Park, Washington (not in file, SVP, Family Office, December 4, 2007); Westchester Land Trust; Whooping Crane Conservation Association; Wild Waterbird Conservancy Inc.; Wilderness Research Foundation Inc.; Write Source; Wyoming OUtdoor Council; Wyoming Wildlife Federation.
  - Accokeek Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - American Conservation Association, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - American Conservation Trust, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Audubon Magazine, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Audubon New York, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Center for Sustainable Fisheries, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Conservation Fund, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Craighead Environmental Research Institute, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Earth Charter, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Friends of the Rockefeller State Park Preserve, 2001-2006 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Cora Hartshorn Arboretum and Bird Sanctuary, 2001-2006 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Island Resources Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve Inc., 2001-2006 (Box 15, Folder 3-4, Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Lady Bird Johnson Wildflower Center, 2001-2006 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Land and Water Conservation Fund (Americans for Our Heritage and Recreation), 2001-2006 (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
  - Minneapolis Parks Legacy Society, 2001-2006 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Murie Center, 2001-2006 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - National Audubon Society, 2001-2006 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - National Fish and Wildlife Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - National Parks Conservation Association, 2001-2006 (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
  - National Recreation and Park Association, 2001-2006 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 2001-2006 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Natural Resources Council of America, 2001-2006 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Nature Conservancy, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Nature Conservancy of New York and of Hawaii.
  - Northern Forest Center, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Open Space Institute, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Resources for the Future, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - River Network, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Shelburne Farms, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Student Conservation Association Inc., 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Vermont Land Trust, 2001-2006 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society, 2001-2006 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
  - World Wildlife Fund, 2001-2006 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Multiple States (MS) - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Multiple States (MS) - Vermont - Vermont Institute of Natural Science, 2001-2006 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Multiple States (MS) - Wyoming - Jackson Hole Land Trust, 2001-2006 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - New York City - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Includes: Leadership Committee of Parks 2001; New York Harbor Parks Project; Parks Council; Plant-A-Lot; River End Estuaries Center; Trees New York.
  - New York City - Central Park Conservancy, 2001-2006 (Box 20, Folder 3-5)
  - New York City - City Parks Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - New York City - Council on the Environment of New York City, 2001-2006 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - New York City - Heather Garden (Fort Tryon Park), 2001-2006 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - New York City - New Yorkers for Parks, 2001-2006 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - New York City - New York Parks and Conservation Association, 2001-2006 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - New York State - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Includes: Friends of the Palisades Interstate Park; New York Rivers United; New York State Office of Parks, Recreation, and Historic Preservation; Parks and Trails New York; Riverkeeper; Rivers and Estuaries Center; Rivers and Estuaries Research Advisory Committee; Scenic America.
  - New York State - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 2001-2006 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - New York State - Scenic Hudson, 2001-2006 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - United States Government - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Includes: Great Sand Dunes National Park; Great Smoky Mountains National Park; Greater Yellowstone Coalition; Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial Grove; William Penn Mott, Jr. Memorial Fund; National Parks Project for Youth in Leadership; National Parks Trust; Virgin Islands National Park.
  - United States Government - Department of the Interior - Grand Teton National Park Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Foundation, 2001-2006 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service, 2001-2006 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - Steve Martin, 2001-2006 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - United States Government - Marsh-Billings - Rockefeller National Historical Park, 2001-2006 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Education, 2001-2006; 6
  - Education - A-Z, 2001-2006 (Box 23, Folder 5-8)